citydeals.com 2015-12-22

# Customer Service

  * Terms That Apply to All Deals
  * Shipping & Delivery
  * Privacy & Security
  * Return Policy
  * Ordering
  * Availability & Pricing
  * Account Information

This site is powered by Super Saver Media. The Super Saver Media offices are located in Bluffdale, UT. Any references to “we”, “our”, or “us” in these terms are referring to Super Saver Media and the company that owns this website. contact us.

**Terms That Apply to All Deals**
     The following terms apply to all deals on the site unless otherwise specified in the Fine Print or prohibited by law: 

  * Not valid with other offers, discounts, or promotions 
  * Not valid for cash back 
  * May not be used to purchase gift cards or gift certificates 
  * Not valid for tax or gratuity 
  * Vouchers have a promotional value and paid value. The paid value is the amount a customer pays for the voucher. The promotional value is the amount of the discount (the full value of the voucher minus the amount paid for it). The promotional value expires on the expiration date listed on the voucher. The paid value never expires.

**Shipping & Delivery**
    Some offers are subject to shipment contracts with third party carriers. We will do everything possible on our end to make sure items are properly shipped; however, we are not responsible if a voucher is lost, stolen, destroyed, or used without your permission once the shipment has been turned over to third party carriers. Although we strive to be as accurate as possible with shipping and delivery times they are only estimates and we are not liable for any shipping delays. 

We are not responsible for damaged product received through a third party carrier (UPS, FedEx, or USPS), which is out of our control. We are not responsible for shipments undeliverable as a result of incorrect address information supplied to us. We will attempt to contact the customer to resolve the error. 

Shipments that total more than $299.00 will be shipped via Express or Priority shipping methods and will require a signature upon delivery. 

Please contact us immediately if there is a shipping error due to a mistake we made. You can rest assured we will take care of it. In the event the wrong product is shipped to you, we will gladly replace it with the correct items when the incorrect products have been returned to us via a trackable method. Return postage for incorrect orders can be provided by contacting customer service.

**Privacy & Security**

     This privacy policy sets out how we use and protects any information that you give us when you use this website. We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. 

We may collect the following information: 

  * Name and job title 
  * Contact information including email address 
  * Demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests 
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and offers 

We require this information for the following reasons: 

  * To understand your needs and provide you with a better service. 
  * Internal record keeping. 
  * To improve our products and services. 
  * To periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers, or other information which we think you may find interesting. 
  * To contact you for market research purposes (through email, phone, fax, or mail). 
  * To customize the website according to your interests. 

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences. 

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. 

You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at the contact links provided on this website. 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 for a fee of $10. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to Super Saver Media 14441 S 980 W Ste 200 Bluffdale, UT 84065. 

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to us at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

**  
Return Policy**

We want to make sure you have a great experience using every voucher you purchase from us. If you ever have a poor experience using a voucher purchased on this site, please let us know immediately. 

If you change your mind about a deal you purchase on this site, you may [contact us](http://www.vpdealz.net/index.php/contacts/index/) within 7 days of your purchase to return any unredeemed voucher for a full refund, unless the voucher is for an event that has already past. 

In addition, if a business refuses to honor your voucher in accordance with the terms outlined on the deal, you may return the voucher to us for a refund within 7 days and a store credit thereafter, as long as the voucher isn’t expired and hasn’t been redeemed.

**Ordering**

We use a secure server for your privacy and security. Online payment may be made using Visa, MasterCard, and Discover credit and debit cards. Credit cards are processed and money is collected by Super Saver Media. When you are ready to check out you will be taken to a secure section of this site. You will be asked to fill out information, including, but not limited to: your name, your billing address, your phone number, your email, your card type, card number, card CVV code, and card expiration date.

**Availability & Pricing**

Due to the nature of our products and the relationships with our merchants, pricing and product availability can and will change frequently. 

We will occasionally offer promotional for extra discounts. These promotions are only valid under the exact terms they were offered. We are unable to back date or extend any sales, specials, discounts, or promotional codes for orders that have already been placed.

**Account Information**

If you have an account with us, you will be able view your account information and order history in your account. You can view and update your account information anytime by clicking on the “My Account“ link at the top of the homepage.

Subscribe to our deals! 

Save up to 90% on CityDeals.com 

Save on restaurants, fun, spas, hotels and more! We'll never rent, sell, or share your email.
